Contact

prateeknarang111@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/prateek-narang-0108b39a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

C++

JavaScript

Python

Languages

Hindi (Professional Working)

English (Professional Working)

Punjabi (Professional Working)

Honors-Awards

Code For India Hackathon Winner

Smart City Hackathon Winner

CoDelhi Hackathon Winner

Spython Game Development

Challenge Winner

Google DART Hackathon RunnerUp

Publications

Maps Vs Unordered Maps : A Performance analysis on large datasets

Prateek Narang

Trained 35,000+ Coders so far | Co-founder, Coding Blocks North West Delhi

Summary

Experienced code mentor & programmer with a demonstrated history of working in the professional training & coding industry. Skilled in C++, Python, Machine Learning & Data Science, Data Structures and Algorithms. Strong professional with a MS(Research) focused in Machine Learning, Deep Learning & Al from Indian Institute of Technology, Delhi.

Experience

Coding Blocks

5 years 1 month

Cofounder

June 2016 - Present (4 years 3 months)

New Delhi Area, India

Mentor

August 2015 - Present (5 years 1 month)

Delhi

SanDisk

Firmware Engineer

June 2015 - July 2015 (2 months)

HackerEarth

Intern

March 2015 - May 2015 (3 months)

Problem Setter & Evaluator

Veddis Labs

Intern

July 2014 - August 2014 (2 months)

Education

Delhi Technological University (Formerly DCE)

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (2012 - 2016)

Indian Institute of Technology, Delhi

MS(Research), Machine Learning, Deep Learning & AI · (2018 - 2020)

Delhi College of Engineering

Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.), Computer Engineering · (2012 - 2016)

Swami Sant Dass Public School